

WEB DEVELOPER

<u> iordihernandez133@gmail.com</u>

• P.O. Box 391, Bridgeport WA, 98813, United States of America

L 509-733-1795

Details

Nationality
Mexican/American

Summary

Hi, my name is Jordi Hernandez. I grew up in Bridgeport WA. In my short two decades of life I've mastered a number of things. Such as farm work, elderly caregiving, phone repairs, auto repair, athletics, firefighting (structural and wildland). These previous occupations helped me develop experience in teamwork, problem solving, leadership, team project management. Thanks to the knowledge and experience gained from these occupations the door has opened to pursue a life long career as a web developer.

Education

Coding-Bootcamp Computer Programming, UW Professional & Continuing Education

January 2021 — December 2022

Full stack certificate, UW Professional & Continuing Education

January 2021 — December 2022

Bridgeport High School

January 2013 — December 2017

Links

www.linkedin.com/in/jordi-hernandez-b731b7223

Courses

Coding Bootcamp

Experience

Sales Person, JCPenney, Spokane

October 2018 — March 2022

- -Responsibilities as sales associate were to greet customers and help them in any needs they required around the store.
- -The impact I helped deliver was an increase of customer satisfaction. Including a 6% percent increase in credit card applications among customers.
- I received employee of the week for the above mentioned 6% increase in credit card application.

Swim Instructor, Samantha's Swimming, Spokane

October 2018 — June 2019

- -Responsibilities: Pass down swimming knowledge, safety, and responsibilities to any swimmer regardless of age.
- -The Impact I've delivered to my students led them to successfully learn a variety of swimming strokes such as crawl stroke, breast stroke, back stroke and butterfly stroke at a rate of 99%.

Volunteer Firefighter, Douglas/Okanogan County, Douglas/Okanogan County

March 2016 — June 2017

- -Volunteer firefighter for Okanogan/Douglas Counties
- -learned how to extinguish structural and wild land fires in the safest manner possible.

Security Guard, Allied Universal, Spokane

February 2018 — May 2021

- -Performed security services for Walmart and Amazon.
- -This position further drove my skills in teamwork, awareness, and safety.

Firefighter, Methow River Wild Fire, Carlton

June 2017 — Present

- -Seasonal summer job in which I grew from a Firefighter Type 2 (FFT2) to a Squad Boss in order to run as an Engine Boss (ENGB).
- -This job taught me how to problem solve, lead, and make the best decisions possible under extreme pressure in life or death situations in order to suppress and contain fire in the swiftest and safest way possible.
- -Acquired the skills to successfully work and lead a happy crew of constant changing people with variety of personalities.

Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure	Problem Solving
Communication	Teamwork
Adaptability	Strong Leadership Skills
Programming Languages	•
References	
Moises Ceja	Brandon Quaschnick from Allied
951-452-4267	Universal

509-990-5334

Andres Munoz

206-427-9524